A Guide to the Records of Julian A. Burruss, President, Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1906-1946
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Series 4: Subject Files
  - Subseries 1: Physical Plant, 1922-1929
    - Carneal & Johnston Stone Dormitory, 1929 (Box-folder 23-1560)
    - Carneal & Johnston Stone Dormitory - Orders, 1929 (Box-folder 23-1561)
    - Carneal & Johnston - Telegrams, 1926-29 (Box-folder 23-1562)
    - Bids for Improvements to Central Heating Plant, 1928 (Box-folder 23-1563)
    - Chairs & Other Equipment W.M.H., 1926 (Box-folder 23-1564)
    - Chairs, Shades, & etc., 1927-28 (Box-folder 23-1565)
    - Chemistry Building, 1926-1927 (Box-folder 23-1566)
    - Contracts, Agreements, Etc., 1929 (Box-folder 23-1567)
    - J.L. Crouse Contractor, 1925-26 (Box-folder 23-1568)
    - J.L. Crouse Contractor, 1926 (Box-folder 23-1569)
    - J.L. Crouse Contracts, 1927 (Box-folder 23-1570)
    - Davidson Hall, 1929 (Box-folder 23-1571)
    - Dormitory No. 1, Noell Act, 1926 (Box-folder 23-1572)
    - F.W. Eheart, Representing Town of Blacksburg, 1929 (Box-folder 23-1573)
    - Fidelity & Casualty Co. - Bailer Report, 1927 (Box-folder 23-1574)
    - Harris, Contractor - Heating W.M.H. & Library, 1926 (Box-folder 23-1575)
    - Haymes Construction Co. Contractor, 1929 (Box-folder 23-1576)
      - VT construction
    - Heating War Memorial Hall & Library, 1926 (Box-folder 23-1577)
    - Hoback/Painter, 1928 (Box-folder 23-1578)
    - H.A. Lucas Contractor, 1926-1927 (Box-folder 23-1579)
    - Maintenance, Replacement, Repair, 1944 (Box-folder 23-1580)
    - J.B. McCrary Engineering Corporation re Sewerage Disposal System Correspondence Closed, 1929 (Box-folder 23-1581)
    - Bid Heating Equipment Mechanics Arts Building, 1928 (Box-folder 23-1582)
    - Patton Engineering Hall, 1925-26 (Box-folder 23-1583)
    - D.J. Phipps Contractor, 1927 (Box-folder 23-1584)
    - D.J. Phipps Contractor, 1929 (Box-folder 23-1585)
    - Physical Plant Committee/Chairman's Misc. Matters, 1924-27 (Box-folder 23-1586)
    - Physical Plant Committee, Prof. Johnston & Others, 1924-1927 (Box-folder 23-1587)
    - Physical Plant Committee, 1925-1929 (Box-folder 23-1588)
    - The Physical Plant Con., Prof. Johnson & Others, 1926-1928 (Box-folder 23-1589)
    - Physical Plant Comm., Prof. Johnson & Others, 1926-1927 (Box-folder 23-1590)
    - The Physical Plant, Prof. Johnson & Others, 1927 (Box-folder 23-1591)
    - Physical Plant Committee Sewerage Plant Matters, 1929 (Box-folder 23-1592)
    - Physical Plant Committee on Power House, 1929 (Box-folder 23-1593)
    - Power Plant, 1929 (Box-folder 23-1594)
    - Power Plant Equipment, 1929 (Box-folder 23-1595)
    - Power Plant/Turbine, 1929 (Box-folder 23-1596)
    - Remodeling Science Hall, Dormitory No. 2, 1929 (Box-folder 23-1597)
    - Draft & Final Reports, 1929 (Box-folder 23-1598)
    - Requisitions, 1929 (Box-folder 23-1599)
      - Report continuation
    - Roads, Walks, Sewer/Prof. Begg & Others, 1926-28 (Box-folder 23-1600)
    - R.I. Roop, Attorney, 1929 (Box-folder 23-1601)
      - Troy Simmons v. V.P.I.
      - Easement of old Edward Black farm
    - Sewerage Disposal System, 1929 (Box-folder 23-1602)
    - Simpson-Basham Co., Plumbing & Heating, 1927 (Box-folder 23-1603)
    - War Memorial Hall Matters (Miscellaneous), 1925-1926 (Box-folder 23-1604)
    - F.L. Watson Heating Contractor, 1926 (Box-folder 23-1605)
    - F.L. Watson, 1929 (Box-folder 23-1606)
    - Wiley & Wilson, Dormitory No. 1, 1926-1927 (Box-folder 23-1607)
    - Wiley & Wilson, War Memorial Hall, 1926 (Box-folder 23-1608)
    - Wiley & Wilson Chemistry Building, 1927 (Box-folder 23-1609)
    - Wiley & Wilson, Heating Engineers, 1927 (Box-folder 23-1610)
    - Wiley & Wilson Orders etc., 1927-1929 (Box-folder 23-1611)
    - Wiley & Wilson-Engrs. Patton Hall & Admin. Bldg, 1925-26 (Box-folder 23-1612)
    - Wiley & Wilson Hospital, 1929 (Box-folder 23-1613)
    - Wiley & Wilson Orders, 1929 (Box-folder 23-1614)
    - Wiley & Wilson, Science Hall & Engineers, 1927 (Box-folder 23-1615)
    - Wiley & Wilson Miscellaneous Matters, 1929 (Box-folder 23-1616)
      - End of report
    - Wiley & Wilson, 1929 (Box-folder 23-1617)
    - Wiley & Wilson Stone Dorm & Patton Hall, 1929 (Box-folder 24-1618)
    - Special Wiley & Wilson Power Plant, 1929 (Box-folder 24-1619)
      - Power Plant Blueprint - copy of deed to New Power Plant from Alexander and Lizzie Black.
    - S.B. & Lee H. Williamson, 1926-1929 (Box-folder 24-1620)
    - Working Papers #1, 1929 (Box-folder 24-1621)
  - Subseries 2: Physical Plant, 1928-1944
    - Agricultural Building - Bids - General, 1939-40 (Box-folder 24-1622)
    - Application for Loan & Grant, 1933-34 (Box-folder 24-1623)
    - Supplementary Application for Allotment, 1935 (Box-folder 24-1624)
    - Armory, 1936 (Box-folder 24-1625)
    - Supervising Architect, 1930 (Box-folder 24-1626)
    - J.F. Barbour & Son, 1935-39 (Box-folder 24-1627)
    - J.F. Barbour & Son, 1935 (Box-folder 24-1628)
    - Bids - General, 1935-36 Furniture Advertisements and Specifications (Box-folder 24-1629)
    - Bids - Quarrying Stone for all Buildings, 1934 (Box-folder 24-1630)
    - Bids - Staff, Dorm, & Utilities Building, 1934-37 (Box-folder 24-1631)
    - Bidders not Awarded Contracts, 1930 (Box-folder 24-1632)
    - Board of Visitors - Authorizations, 1938-40 (Box-folder 24-1633)
    - Bond - Sale Data for Prospective Purchasers, 1938 (Box-folder 24-1634)
    - Bond Sales (Brokers & Other Than PWA), 1934-37 (Box-folder 24-1635)
    - Budget Allotments/PWA Op./Admin. Bldg/Dorms, 1942-44 (Box-folder 24-1636)
    - Carneal & Johnston, 1928-30 (Box-folder 24-1637)
    - Carneal, Johnston, & Wright Hospital, 1929-30 (Box-folder 24-1638)
    - Carneal, Johnston, & Wright Orders, 1929-30 (Box-folder 24-1639)
    - Carneal, Johnston, & Wright-Architects, 1930-37 (Box-folder 24-1640)
    - C, J, & W (Carneal, Johnston, & Wright) General, 1933-37 (Box-folder 24-1641)
    - C, J, & W - Future General, 1938 (Box-folder 24-1642)
    - C, J, & W General, 1938-41 (Box-folder 24-1643)
    - C, J, & W - Proposed Buildings - Preliminary, 1938 (Box-folder 24-1644)
    - Carneal, Johnston, & Wright-Valves, etc., 1943 (Box-folder 24-1645)
    - Chemical Engineering Building, 1937-38 (Box-folder 24-1646)
    - Chemical Engineering Building, 1936-37 (Box-folder 24-1647)
    - Davidson Hall (Chem. Eng.) - Bids - General, 1937-38 (Box-folder 25-1648)
    - Conduit & Pool, 1934 (Box-folder 25-1649)
    - Contracts - Architects, etc., 1939 (Box-folder 25-1650)
    - Contract Changes, 1939-40 (Box-folder 25-1651)
    - Contracts - Completion & Acceptance, 1939-40 (Box-folder 25-1652)
    - Contracts - Extension of Time, 1939-40 (Box-folder 25-1653)
    - Davidson Hall Completion (1), 1932-33 (Box-folder 25-1654)
    - Davidson Hall Completion (2), 1930-32 (Box-folder 25-1655)
    - Davidson Hall (addition), 1932 (Box-folder 25-1656)
    - Dining Hall - Bids - General, 1939-41 (Box-folder 25-1657)
    - Dormitories - Bids - General, 1938-39 (Box-folder 25-1658)
    - Dormitories, 1938-39 (Box-folder 25-1659)
    - Dorm Unit #4/Bids, Payments, Correspondence, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 25-1660)
    - Electric Line Extensions, 1935 (Box-folder 25-1661)
    - Electricity, Steam, Grading, Landscaping - College Dept. Connections, 1934-36 (Box-folder 25-1662)
    - Elevators, May 1930 (Box-folder 25-1663)
    - Engineering Building, 1938-40 (Box-folder 25-1664)
    - Equipment, 1938-40 (Box-folder 25-1665)
    - E.R. Evans (General), 1934-35 (Box-folder 25-1666)
    - Faculty Dorm, 1934 (Box-folder 25-1667)
    - Faculty Dorm, PWA #1, 1935 (Box-folder 25-1668)
    - Faculty Dorm, PWA #2, 1935-37 (Box-folder 25-1669)
    - Financial Estimates - Payment of Interest, Principle, & SKG FD Revenue, 1935-38 (Box-folder 25-1670)
    - 1st National Exchange Bank, 1934-37 (Box-folder 25-1671)
    - J.V. Gary, 1934-36 (Box-folder 25-1672)
    - J.V. Gary, 1936-39 (Box-folder 25-1673)
    - Gary, J.V., 1938 (Box-folder 25-1674)
    - Grant VA 1284-F Final Settlement, 1940-41 (Box-folder 25-1675)
    - Hawkins, Delafield, & Longfellow, 1934 (Box-folder 25-1676)
    - Heating Connections - Bids - General, 1939-40 (Box-folder 25-1677)
    - House - Moving, 1934-36 (Box-folder 25-1678)
    - Inclinerator & Garbage Building, 1939-40 (Box-folder 26-1679)
    - Insurance & Bands (Contractors), 1934-37 (Box-folder 26-1680)
    - Loan & Grant Agreement, 1934 (Box-folder 26-1681)
    - Natural Science Lab (proposed Bailey Museum Bldg), 1937-39 (Box-folder 26-1682)
    - New Dormitory (addition), 1930 (Box-folder 26-1683)
    - Newspaper Clippings & Articles for Publication, 1930-35 (Box-folder 26-1684)
      - Newspaper Clipping outlining various new buildings and campus additions-Burruss Hall/Auditorium; Donaldson-Brown Hotel et. al.
    - Old Dining Hall - Bids - General, 1938-39 (Box-folder 26-1685)
    - Payments, Revenue, & Expenses, 1934-38 Budget (Box-folder 26-1686)
    - Pm't- Interest & Principle 1790-1053-1215-1284, 1937-38 (Box-folder 26-1687)
    - Payments from Construction Fund, 1938-40 (Box-folder 26-1688)
    - Physical Plant Committee, 1929-30 (Box-folder 26-1689)
    - Physical Plant Committee/Col. Johnson & Others, 1929-31 (Box-folder 26-1690)
    - Physical Plant - General, 1921-34 (Box-folder 26-1691)
      - Map of proposed roadway entrance to the camp.
      - Map of proposed campus development plans.
      - Insurance figures on buildings and equipment.
    - Physical Plant/Possible Additional Projects, 1937-41 (Box-folder 26-1692)
    - Physical Plant/Buildings & Grounds/Proposed Reorganization, 1942 (Box-folder 26-1693)
    - Power Plant, 1930 (Box-folder 26-1694)
    - PWA Advertising (for bids), 1934-36 (Box-folder 26-1695)
    - PWA Buildings - conduit, pool, sewers, water tank, 1934 (Box-folder 26-1696)
    - PWA Bids - Faculty Dorm, 1934-36 (Box-folder 26-1697)
    - PWA Faculty Dorm, 1934 (Box-folder 26-1698)
    - P.W.A./Equipment/S.A.B./Miscellaneous, 1934-37 (Box-folder 26-1699)
    - P.W.A./History, 1934-35 (Box-folder 26-1700)
    - PWA Regional Director - Atlanta, 1938-40 (Box-folder 26-1701)
    - PWA - General - Atlanta - D.C.- Resident Eng., 1938-40 (Box-folder 26-1702)
    - Account Voucher 148435-44 to 151051, 1926 (Box-folder 26-1703)
    - Supplemental Account Vouchers 1043-1290, 1919-20 (Box-folder 26-1704)
    - Force Account Vouchers, 1934-35 (Box-folder 26-1705)
    - PWA-Price Inquiries-Force Accounts, 1934 (2 folder) (Box-folder 26-1706 to 26-1707)
    - PWA Invoices #1-99, 1934 (Box-folder 26-1708)
    - PWA Invoices #1000-1599, 1934-35 (Box-folder 26-1709)
    - PWA Invoices #1600-1746, 1935 (Box-folder 27-1710)
    - PWA Vouchers #1851-1907, 1934-37 (Box-folder 27-1711)
    - PWA Vouchers #1908-1983, 1934-37 (Box-folder 26-1712)
    - Misc.-Public Works, etc., 1934 (Box-folder 27-1713)
    - Public Works Reserve-Planning Branch of the PWA, 1941 (Box-folder 27-1714)
    - Refrigerating Units/Insulation/Cold Storage Doors, 1928, 1930 (Box-folder 27-1715)
    - Requisitions for Grants, 1934-36--Grant funding document (Box-folder 27-1716 and 27-1716A)
    - Requisitions For Loans, 1934-36 (Box-folder 27-1717)
    - Roads, Walks, Sewers, etc., 1927-31 (Box-folder 27-1718)
    - S.A.B. - Application Prelim., 1935-36 (Box-folder 27-1719)
    - S.A.B. Bids, 1936 (Box-folder 27-1720)
    - S.A.B. - C. J. & W., 1936 (Box-folder 27-1721)
    - S.A.B. - Financial Payments/Agreements/Loans, 1936-37 (Box-folder 27-1722)
    - S.A.B. Kitchen & Dining Room, 1937 (Box-folder 27-1723)
    - S.A.B.-Legal/J.V. Gary/Official; State Engrs. Office, 1934-36 (Box-folder 27-1724)
    - S.A.B. Operations, 1936-37 (Box-folder 27-1725)
    - S.A.B., 1935-7/1/36 (Box-folder 27-1726)
    - S.A.B., 7/1/36-11/1/36 (Box-folder 27-1727)
    - S.A.B., 11/1/36-2/1/37 (Box-folder 27-1728)
    - S.A.B., 2/1/37 (Box-folder 27-1729)
    - Sewer Water Tank, 1933-36 (Box-folder 27-1730)
    - Space Assignment, 1939-40 (Box-folder 27-1731)
    - State Engineer, 1933-35 (Box-folder 27-1732)
    - State Engineering, 1935-37 (Box-folder 27-1733)
    - State Gov. Bldg Dir., Treasurer, General Assembly, 1933-36 (Box-folder 27-1734)
    - State Offices - Laws, etc., 1938-39 (Box-folder 27-1735)
    - Stein, F.J., 1934-36 (Box-folder 27-1736)
    - Stone Quarrying, 1934-35 (Box-folder 28-1737)
    - Stone Quarrying - Bids, 1938-40 (Box-folder 28-1738)
    - Student Dorm, 1934-37 (Box-folder 28-1739)
    - Student Dorm & Utilities, 1934-36 Building Projects continued. (Box-folder 28-1740)
    - Extras, Credits & Approvals of Sub Contracts, 1934-37 (Box-folder 28-1741)
    - Swimming Pool, 1932-33 (Box-folder 28-1742)
    - T & A Building Bids, 1934-36 (Box-folder 28-1743)
    - T & A Building, 1934--Campus Placement of Buildings (Box-folder 28-1744)
    - T & A Building 1/1/35-6/30/35--Building Composition (Box-folder 28-1745)
    - T & A Building 7/1/35-12/31/35 (Box-folder 28-1746)
    - T & A Building, 1/1/36-3/31/36 (Box-folder 28-1747)
    - T & A Building 4/1/36-37--Piano Advertisements (Box-folder 28-1748)
    - Utilities Building, 1934-37 (Box-folder 28-1749)
    - VPI Dept. Services, etc., 1938-39 (Box-folder 28-1750)
    - Watson, F.L., 1930 (Box-folder 28-1751)
    - Wiley & Wilson, 1930-34 (Box-folder 28-1752)
    - Wilson, I. D., Res. Engineer Inspector, 1934-36 (Box-folder 28-1753)
- Series 5: Virginia State Survey, 1929-1930
  - Arlington County, 1929 (Box-folder 28-1754)
    - Survey
  - Bedford County, 1929 (Box-folder 28-1755)
    - Survey
  - Bland County, 1930 (Box-folder 28-1756)
  - H. K. Bowen, 1928 (Box-folder 28-1757)
  - H. K. Bowen, 1929 (Box-folder 28-1758)
  - H. K. Bowen, 1930 (Box-folder 28-1759)
  - H.K. Bowen, 1931-1935 (Box-folder 28-1760)
  - Buchanan County, 1930 (Box-folder 28-1761)
  - Craig County, 1930 (Box-folder 28-1862)
  - Dickenson County, 1930 (Box-folder 28-1763)
  - Farmville - Town, 1930 (Box-folder 28-1764)
    - Survey
    - Chemical analysis of water in Giles county
    - Industrial survey of Giles county
  - Floyd County, 1930 (Box-folder 28-1765)
  - Giles County - Virginia Corr. in Regard to Survey, 1929 (Box-folder 28-1766)
  - Request for Giles County Survey, 1930 (Box-folder 28-1767)
  - Grayson County - VA Corr. In Regard to Survey, 1929 (Box-folder 28-1768)
    - Dr. R.J. Holden and Hillsville sheriff in car-smashing incident
  - Halifax County, 1930 (Box-folder 28-1769)
  - Lee County, 1930 (Box-folder 28-1770)
  - H.E. Mecredy, 1930 (Box-folder 28-1771)
  - Montgomery Co. - VA Corr. In Regard to Survey, 1929 (Box-folder 28-1772)
  - Orange County, 1929-1930 (Box-folder 28-1773)
  - Portsmouth, VA Corr. In Regard to Survey, 1930 (Box-folder 28-1774)
  - Pulaski County, 1930 (Box-folder 28-1775)
  - Roanoke County, 1930 (Box-folder 28-1776)
  - Russell County, 1930 (Box-folder 28-1777)
  - Scott County, 1930 (Box-folder 28-1778)
  - Shenandoah County, 1930 (Box-folder 28-1779)
  - Smyth County, 1930 (Box-folder 28-1780)
  - Suffolk Survey Correspondence, 1930 (Box-folder 28-1781)
  - Request for Suffolk Survey, 1930 (Box-folder 29-1782)
  - North Tazewell, VA Corr. In Regard to Survey, 1930 (Box-folder 29-1783)
  - Request for Tazewell Survey, 1930 (Box-folder 29-1784)
  - Washington County, 1930 (Box-folder 29-1785)
  - Wise County, VA Corr. In Regard to Survey, 1930 (Box-folder 29-1786)
  - Wythe County, 1928-1929 (Box-folder 29-1787)
  - Request for Wytheville Survey, 1930 (Box-folder 29-1788)
  - Misc.-Industrial Survey Work and Staff, 1929 (Box-folder 29-1789)
  - Misc.-Industrial Survey, Census Bureau, 1930 (Box-folder 29-1790)
  - Bureau of Community Development, Enrollment Stats, Industrial Development of SW VA, 1931 (Box-folder 29-1791)
  - Request for Surveys, 1930 (Box-folder 29-1792)
  - Req. for Surveys, Referred to Mr. Bowen & Others, 1930 (Box-folder 29-1793)
  - Request for Surveys of Different Towns & Cities, 1930 (Box-folder 29-1794)
  - State Survey Correspondence, 1931-32 (Box-folder 29-1795)
  - State Survey, 1930 (Box-folder 29-1796 to 29-1797)
  - State Survey: Transportation Survey, 1931 (Box-folder 29-1798)
  - Topical Outlines for Industrial Surveys, 1930 (Box-folder 29-1799)
  - Special Mailing List, 1930 (Box-folder 29-1800)
  - Booklet for South Western Virginia, Elec., 1930 (Box-folder 29-1801)
    - Lists of hospitals, hotels...for Bristol and other Southwestern Virginia towns
  - State Conservation & Development Commission, 1930 (Box-folder 29-1802)
  - Department of Labor and Industry, 1929 (Box-folder 29-1803)
  - Virginia Industry, 1928-1929 (Box-folder 29-1804)
- Series 6: Subject Files
  - Subseries 1: Subject Files, 1919-1928
    - Administrative Council, 1921 (Box-folder 29-1805)
    - Agricultural Certificates of Merit, 1924 (Box-folder 29-1806)
    - Agricultural Experiment Station, 1919-20 (Box-folder 29-1807)
    - Ag. Schools & Teachers, 1919-1920 (Box-folder 29-1808)
    - Alcohol, Student Pledge Regarding, 1922 (Box-folder 29-1809)
    - Allen Report, 1919 (Box-folder 29-1810)
    - All-Virginia Party, 1926 (Box-folder 29-1811)
    - Alumni, 1922-27 (Box-folder 29-1812)
      - World War Memorial Fund.
      - Dedication Program for World War Memorial Hall and Stadium.
    - American Association of University Women, 1926-27 (Box-folder 29-1813)
    - American Bankers Association (Educational Foundation), 1928 (Box-folder 29-1814)
    - Annual Reports, 1922-26 (Box-folder 29-1815)
    - Apartment Buildings & Residence (Box-folder 29-1816)
    - Applications, appointments, etc, 1922-1928 (Box-folder 29-1817)
    - Appropriations for Dept. of Instruction, 1919-1920 (Box-folder 29-1818)
    - Association of Colleges & Secondary Schools, 1923-28 (Box-folder 29-1819)
    - Athletics, 1924-25 (Box-folder 29-1820)
    - Statements of Auditing Committee, 1920 (Box-folder 30-1821)
    - The Band, 1921 (Box-folder 30-1822)
    - Bonds, 1919-1936 (Box-folder 30-1823)
    - Biennial Budget Matters, 1926-1928 (Box-folder 30-1824)
    - Borchure for VPI, 1943 (Box-folder 30-1825)
    - Budget, 1920 (Box-folder 30-1826)
    - Budget, 1920-1922 (Box-folder 30-1827)
    - Working Budget, 1920-1924 (Box-folder 30-1828)
    - Budget, 1922-1924 (Box-folder 30-1829)
    - Bug File, 1922-1929 (Box-folder 30-1830)
      - misc. ltrs. & notes on unsolicited opinions
    - Buildings-Valuation, 1922 (Box-folder 30-1831)
    - Burruss-Efforts to Gain VPI Presidency, 1919 (Box-folder 30-1832)
    - Can state institution under budget system pay expenses of students to conferences, etc, 1925 (Box-folder 30-1833)
    - Mailing List Requests to COCs, 1928 (Box-folder 30-1834)
    - Chemistry Graduates, 1925 (Box-folder 30-1835)
    - Commission Blanket Letters, 1928 (Box-folder 30-1836)
      - 1928 General Assembly report authorizing the study of conditions of farmers in Virginia.
    - Constitution & By-Laws Corps of Cadets (Box-folder 30-1837)
    - Cost per Student per Session, 1924-1925 (Box-folder 30-1838)
    - Crop Pest Matters (Box-folder 30-1839)
    - Curriculum Development, 1919-1920 (Box-folder 30-1840)
    - Curricula Development, 1920 (Box-folder 30-1841)
    - Curricula Development, 1921-1922 (Box-folder 30-1842)
    - Curricula Development, 1922-1923 (Box-folder 30-1843)
    - Davidson Hall, the Naming of, 1927 (Box-folder 30-1844)
    - Departmental Reports, 1928 (Box-folder 30-1845)
    - Honorary Degrees, 1928 (Box-folder 30-1846)
    - Directory of Faculty & Administrative Officers, 1928 (Box-folder 30-1847)
      - Faculty listing and their degrees.
    - Employment, 1928 (Box-folder 30-1848)
    - Engineering Curricula, 1928 (Box-folder 30-1849)
    - Engineering Experiment Station, 1928 (Box-folder 30-1850)
    - Engineering Exten. Div., 1928 (Box-folder 30-1851)
    - Enrollment Statistics - Questions, 1920 (Box-folder 30-1852)
    - Total Agriculture Enrollment, 1921-1926 (Box-folder 30-1853)
    - Executive Bulletins 1/2/26 - 7/31/26 (Box-folder 30-1854)
    - Experimental Station Financial Reports, 1910-1921 (Box-folder 30-1855)
    - Extension Division, 1918-1923 (Box-folder 30-1856)
    - Annual Reports--Agriculture Department, 1920-1925 (Box-folder 30-1857 to 30-1857A)
    - Annual Report - Agric. Engineering, 1922-1923 (Box-folder 31-1858 to 31-1858A)
    - Annual Report of Extension Work in Agriculture & Home Econonics #1, 1923 (Box-folder 31-1859)
    - An'l Report of Ext. Work in Ag. & Home Economics #2 & #3, 1923 (Box-folder 31-1860)
    - An'l Report of Ext. Work in Ag. & Home Economics #4, 1923 (Box-folder 31-1861)
    - An'l Report of Ext. Work in Ag. & Home Economics #5, 1923 (Box-folder 31-1862)
    - An'l Report of Ext. Work in Ag. & Home Economics #6, 1924 (Box-folder 31-1863)
    - An'l Report of Ext. Work in Ag. & Home Economics #7, 1924 (Box-folder 31-1864)
    - An'l Report of Ext. Work in Ag. & Home Economics #8, 1965 (Box-folder 31-1865)
    - An'l Report of Ext. Work in Ag. & Home Economics #9, 1925 (Box-folder 31-1866)
    - An'l Report of Ext. Work in Ag. & Home Economics #5, 1925 (Box-folder 31-1866A)
    - An'l Report of Ext. Work in Ag. & Home Economics #5, 1925 (Box-folder 31-1866B)
    - An'l Report of Ext. Work in Ag. & Home Economics #5, 1925 (Box-folder 31-1866C)
    - Extension Work in Animal Husbandry, 1921-1925 (Box-folder 31-1867)
    - Annual Report - Director of Extension Work In Virginia, 1923-1924 (Box-folder 31-1868, 31-1868A, and 31-1868B)
    - Extension Report - Food & Nutrition, 1924 (Box-folder 31-1869)
    - Annual Report - State Clothing Specialist, 1923-1924 (Box-folder 31-1870.)
    - Annual Report of State Food Specialists, 1921-1925 (Box-folder 31-1871)
    - Annual Report Virginia Boys Club including pictures of African American Extension workers, farmers, and boys club members, 1921-1922 (Box-folder 31-1872)
    - Extension Suggestions, 1928 (Box-folder 31-1873)
    - Executive Bulletins, 1920-1924 (Box-folder 31-1874 to 31-1874A)
    - Executive Bulletins, 1925 (Box-folder 31-1875)
    - Faculty Positions, Application for, 1920-22 (Box-folder 31-1876)
    - Faculty Questionnaire on Preparation, 1928 (Box-folder 31-1877)
    - Financial Matters, 1919 (Box-folder 31-1878)
    - Foch, Marshall, 1922-23 (Box-folder 31-1879)
    - Form I--For estimating the value of scientific equipment, 1927 (Box-folder 31-1880)
    - Form II--Survey for instructors, 1927 (Box-folder 31-1881)
    - General Assembly, 1922 (Box-folder 31-1882)
    - General Assembly, Miscellaneous Matters, 1924 (Box-folder 31-1883)
    - General Assembly, 1926 (2 folders) (Box-folder 31-1884 to 31-1884A)
    - General Assembly, 1928 (Box-folder 31-1885)
    - General Education Board/Trevor Arnett & Others, 1927 (Box-folder 31-1886)
    - Geology Field Trip, 1929 (Box-folder 31-1887)
    - Graduate Courses, 1927 (Box-folder 31-1888)
    - Accredited Herd Matters, 1920s (Box-folder 31-1889)
    - Holiday Blanks, 1925 (Box-folder 31-1890)
    - Memo Concerning Home Demo Agents, 1920s (Box-folder 31-1891)
    - Regarding Ass'ment of Colleges - Owned Housing, 1920s (Box-folder 31-1892)
    - Influenza Dec. 1928 (Box-folder 31-1893)
    - Institutions of Higher Learning, 1920s (2 folders) (Box-folder 31-1894 to 31-1894A)
    - Deans' Reports on Instruction, 1920-1921 (Box-folder 32-1895)
    - Deans Report on Instruction, 1920s (Box-folder 32-1895A)
    - Deans Third Term Report, 1920s (Box-folder 32-1896)
    - Insurance Valuations, 1922 (Box-folder 32-1897)
    - Investments for Educ. Institutions, Selection of, 1927 (Box-folder 32-1898)
    - Invoices & Insurance Policies, 1923-1924 (Box-folder 32-1899)
    - Knights Templar Loan Fund, 1924-1925 (Box-folder 32-1900)
    - Labor Organizations/Complaints, 1921-22 (Box-folder 32-1901)
    - Livestock Sanitary Board, 1920s (Box-folder 32-1902)
    - Memorandum, 1928 (Box-folder 32-1903)
    - Military Department, 1919-1921 (Box-folder 32-1904)